Finding Aid for Children’s Fund of Michigan records 1929-1965
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Financial 1929-1965
  The series - Financial (1929-1965; 5.5 linear feet and 1 oversize volume) - consists of materials documenting all of the financial operations of the Fund, including budgets, audits, financial statements and reports, and investment reviews. The final series arbitrarily labeled Miscellaneous (1929-ca. 1957; 1.5 linear feet) includes architectural and legal information pertaining to the two children's clinics established by the Fund as well as Green Pastures Camp. Also included are files pertaining to the James Couzens and Maurice Sobell estates. Finally, this series contains information used in the preparation of the 1957 history of the CFM. One of the files labeled "final report" includes transcripts of Norton's interviews with some of the personalities important in CFM history. Portions of these final two series remain unprocessed.
  - Bonds (Box 18)
  - Audits 1930-1965 (Box 18)
  - Budgets (Box 18)
  - Budgets (Child Health Division) 1936-1937 (Box 18)
  - Budgets 1930-1936 (Box 18)
  - Real estate reports 1934-1945, 11 folders (Box 19)
  - Detroit Trust Company
    - General 1929-1946, 1953, 6 folders (Box 19)
    - Investment Review 1946-1954, 17 volumes booklets (Box 20)
    - Financial statements
      - 1932-1947, 10 folders (Box 20)
      - 1948-1953, 6 folders (Box 21)
    - Bonds 1936-1945, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Mortgages 1941-1946 (Box 21)
  - CFM
    - Financial statements and reports
      - 1929-1937, 5 folders (Box 21)
      - 1938-1956 (Box 22)
  - Various financial records (unprocessed; .5 linear feet) (Box 22)
  - Financial journal March 1944-September 1965 (Volume 4)
- Miscellaneous
  (largely unprocessed)
  - Couzens estate (Box 23)
  - Maurice H. Sobell estate (Box 23)
  - CFM final report and interviews (Box 23)
  - Miscellanea re published history of CFM (Box 23)
  - Office and laboratory building (Box 24)
  - Central Michigan Children's Clinic
    - Lease (Box 24)
    - Plumbing contract (Box 24)
    - Orders (Box 24)
    - General contract (Box 24)
    - 1935 contracts, elevators and miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - Superintendent’s salary (Box 24)
    - Electrical contract (Box 24)
  - Northern Michigan Children's Clinic (Box 24)
  - Green Pastures Camp (Box 24)